Finally, let's learn how to make a pair of pants.
First of all, you can use the internal multidirectional line tool
to draw a line that we will use later to cut the internal line.
In the process of drawing, press the Ctrl key and click to create a curve point.
Double click to complete the creation.
After the creation is finished, use the edit version tool to select this line.
Right-click to select Cut.
After the simulation is started, you can see that there is no vermilion between the two panels.
Then we will continue to complete the pocket cloth.
Now we choose the edge of the pocket for this seam.
Here we right-click on this edge to select the panel outline expansion.
After selecting the panel outline expansion, we can set the width of the panel expansion.
In the side corner below,
we need to switch to Extend,
so that it can be expanded according to the original ratio.
After the expansion is completed, click OK.
Don't forget to select the internal line.
This internal line is what we will use to sew the pocket cloth later.
After the panel outline expansion,
there will be a gap between the pocket and the pants panel.
So here we set a negative 1 layer for the pocket.
Because its layer is smaller than the pants 0,
it will automatically fit in after we start the simulation.
After the pocket has been automatically simulated to the inside,
we need to fix the extended part of it on the pants,
that is, to sew with the pants.
So now we have to choose the free sewing tool,
because we haven't set the cut point yet,
so we use the free sewing tool directly.
Click, click.
After sewing,
we also sew the bottom here to the pants panel.
Now, because the side of our pants and pocket are also stacked together,
and then sewed,
so we change the type of sewing line to Turn,
so that it can prevent instability.
Including the sewing line above,
it is the same.
In fact, at this point,
in general, our pants shoes are made like this.
But if you are moving or doing some special actions,
you can see that it is hollow in the middle.
We can fill this pocket.
First of all, we copy and paste this pocket panel,
and cut it along the inner line created before.
Before we officially sew,
we can put the position of this panel first.
Put it almost outside the pocket,
and then we choose this inner line in the middle to cut.
After cutting the inner line,
we delete the excess part.
Now we move the pants to the very outside of this side.
In the 3D space,
we can start to sew after arranging the panel.
First, we sew the top and bottom of this side part.
Also sew to the top of the pants.
Don't forget to change the type of sewing line to Turn.
Then we sew to the top of the pants.
Also sew to the top of the pants.
Then we sew the opening of the side and the opening of the pants together.
Then the bottom of the side and the pocket of the pocket are sewed together.
After creating the model of the charger,
there is one point to note here.
Please note that the inner side and the pants are sewn together, but we have said before that we should not sew across the layer.
Here we first open the simulation to see if it is unstable.
We will see that there is some instability here.
Next, we will deal with the problem of shaking.
First of all, we need to know that the side and the pants can be sewn together.
These two panels are pasted together.
So here we choose the pair between the pants pocket and the pants pocket.
Delete by clicking Delete.
Then we sew the pocket cloth to the side of the pocket.
Remember to change the type of the pocket cloth to Turn.
After the modification, we can see that the side of the simulation is very stable.
There is no such shaking problem.
Finally, we put the middle piece of this piece of cloth.
Now we can see that it is actually facing the back.
We have to choose to turn the surface.
Let it face the same direction.
After completion, we finally return all the layers to the normal state.
That's the end of this video.
See you next time, bye.